<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Software Name: OCARA
  ~
  ~ SPDX-FileCopyrightText: Copyright (c) 2015-2020 Orange
  ~ SPDX-License-Identifier: MPL v2.0
  ~
  ~ This software is distributed under the Mozilla Public License v. 2.0,
  ~ the text of which is available at http://mozilla.org/MPL/2.0/ or
  ~ see the "license.txt" file for more details.
  -->

<resources>
    <!-- about OpenSource-->
    <string name="about_text_1"><b>OCARA</b>, Outil de Contrôle et d’Analyse du Réel Accessible, est avant tout une application permettant d’effectuer un autodiagnostic d’accessibilité des locaux accueillant les salariés. Il fonctionne selon une logique de parcours utilisateur ; grâce à un référentiel élaboré, il permet d’auditer tout type d’objet ou de zone de service, selon une approche multi-handicaps.</string>
    <string name="about_text_2">C’est un outil complet et autonome, qui peut être associé à des référentiels évolutifs et personnalisables.</string>
    <string name="about_text_3">Ocara est développé par les Orange Labs pour la Mission Insertion Handicap d’Orange. Les règles d’accessibilité proposées, inspirées des ERP, ont été élaborées pour les besoins des salariés de l’entreprise. Mais Ocara peut intégrer d’autres référentiels, <b>vos</b> référentiels !</string>
    <string name="about_text_4">Orange a décidé de mettre Ocara en open-source afin que toutes les entreprises, associations ou personnes préoccupés par l’accessibilité, puissent utiliser cet outil et contribuer à son développement.</string>
    <string name="about_text_5">L’accessibilité est une cause commune qui rentre dans le cadre des politiques de Responsabilité Sociale des Entreprises. Elle devrait devenir partie intégrante des politiques de bien-être et de la santé au travail, et un facteur d’efficience sociale.</string>
    <string name="about_text_6">Et c’est en mettant en commun nos moyens, en mutualisant,  que l’on ira plus loin ensemble.</string>


    <string name="about_label_site__OpenSource">C’est sur le site de Meylan, Isère,  que Ocara prend sa source</string>
    <string name="about_mailTo_OpenSource"><b>contact : ocara.support@orange.com</b></string>
    <string name="about_mentions_légales"><b>Mentions légales</b>
androidx - https://developer.android.com/jetpack/androidx
Copyright (C) 2019, The Android Open Source Project
AndroidX is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

material-components-android - https://
Copyright (C) 2019 The Android Open Source Project
material-components-android is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
https://github.com/material-components/material-components-android/blob/master/LICENSE

okhttp3 - https://github.com/square/okhttp
Copyright (C) 2019 Square, Inc.
okhttp3 is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

retrofit2 - https://square.github.io/retrofit/
Copyright (C) 2013 Square, Inc.
retrofit2 is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

ActiveAndroid - https://github.com/pardom/ActiveAndroid
Copyright (C) 2010 Michael Pardo
ActiveAndroid is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

AndroidAnnotations - https://github.com/excilys/androidannotations
Copyright 2012-2015 eBusiness Information
AndroidAnnotations is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

apache commons IO - https://github.com/apache/commons-io
apache commons IO is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

apache POI - https://poi.apache.org/
Copyright 2003-2015 The Apache Software Foundation
apache POI is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

BadgeView - https://github.com/jgilfelt/android-viewbadger
Copyright (c) 2011 readyState Software Ltd.
BadgeView is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

cardview-v7 support library - The Android Open Source Project - https://source.android.com
Copyright (C) 2007 The Android Open Source Project
cardview-v7 is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

jmustache - https://github.com/samskivert/jmustache
Copyright (c) 2010, Michael Bayne
jmustache is distributed under the terms and conditions of the following BSD like license:
https://github.com/samskivert/jmustache/blob/master/LICENSE

PagerSlidingTabStrip - https://github.com/astuetz/PagerSlidingTabStrip
Copyright (C) 2013 Andreas Stuetz andreas.stuetz@gmail.com
PagerSlidingTabStrip is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Picasso - https://github.com/square/picasso
Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.
Picasso is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

holographlibrary - https://bitbucket.org/danielnadeau/holographlibrary
Copyright 2013 The Apache Software Foundation
holographlibrary is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

snackbar - https://github.com/nispok/snackbar
Copyright (c) 2015 William Mora
snackbar is distributed under the terms and conditions of the MIT license
https://github.com/nispok/snackbar/blob/master/LICENSE

Timber - https://github.com/JakeWharton/timber
Copyright 2013 Jake Wharton
Timber is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

TouchImageView - https://github.com/MikeOrtiz/TouchImageView
Copyright (c) 2012 Michael Ortiz
TouchImageView is distributed under the terms and conditions of a BSD like license
https://github.com/MikeOrtiz/TouchImageView/blob/master/LICENSE

TwoWayView - https://github.com/lucasr/twoway-view
Copyright (C) 2013 Lucas Rocha
TwoWayView is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

AndroidPdfViewer - https://github.com/barteksc/AndroidPdfViewer
Copyright 2017 Bartosz Schiller
AndroidPdfViewer is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

gson - https://github.com/google/gson
Copyright 2008 Google Inc.
google gson is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

facebook Stetho - http://facebook.github.io/stetho/
Copyright (c) Facebook, Inc. and its affiliates.
Stetho is distributed under the terms and conditions of the BSD license.
https://opensource.org/licenses/BSD-3-Clause

project lombok - https://www.projectlombok.org
Copyright © 2009-2020 The Project Lombok Authors
projectlombok is distributed under the terms and conditions of the  MIT license.
https://opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php

crashlytics - https://firebase.google.com/terms/crashlytics
Copyright (C) 2020 Google LLC
firebase crashlytics is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

firebase - https://firebase.google.com/terms
Copyright (C) 2020 Google LLC
firebase is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

AppCenter - https://github.com/microsoft/appcenter/blob/master/LICENSE
Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation.
AppCenter is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International Public License
https://github.com/microsoft/appcenter/blob/master/LICENSE

Xamarin - https://github.com/xamarin/Xamarin.Forms/blob/master/LICENSE
Copyright (c) .NET Foundation Contributors
Xamarin is distributed under the terms and conditions of the MIT license.
https://opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php

Robolectric - https://github.com/robolectric/robolectric/blob/master/LICENSE
Copyright (c) 2010 Xtreme Labs, Pivotal Labs and Google Inc.
Robolectric is distributed under the terms and conditions of the  MIT license.
https://opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php

JUnit - https://junit.org/junit4/license.html
Copyright © 2002-2020 JUnit.
JUnit is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Eclipse Public License - v 1.0
https://junit.org/junit4/license.html

AssertJ - https://joel-costigliola.github.io/assertj/
Copyright (C) 2012-2020 the original author or authors.
AssertJ is distributed under the terms and conditions of the Apache License, Version 2.0
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Mockito - https://github.com/mockito/mockito/wiki/License
Copyright (c) 2007 Mockito contributors
Mockito is distributed under the terms and conditions of the  MIT license.
https://opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php
</string>

</resources>